this program is brought to you by
this program is brought to you by Stanford University please visit us at
Stanford University please visit us at
Stanford University please visit us at stanford.edu
you I'm uh honored to be with you today
you I'm uh honored to be with you today for your commencement from one of the
for your commencement from one of the
for your commencement from one of the finest universities in the
finest universities in the
world truth be
world truth be told uh I never graduated from
told uh I never graduated from
told uh I never graduated from college and uh this is the closest I've
college and uh this is the closest I've
college and uh this is the closest I've ever gotten to a college
graduation today I want to tell you
graduation today I want to tell you three stories from my life that's it no
three stories from my life that's it no
three stories from my life that's it no big deal just three
big deal just three
big deal just three stories the first story is about
stories the first story is about
stories the first story is about connecting the dots
connecting the dots
connecting the dots I dropped out of Reed College after the
I dropped out of Reed College after the
I dropped out of Reed College after the first 6 months but then stayed around as
first 6 months but then stayed around as
first 6 months but then stayed around as a drop in for another 18 months or so
a drop in for another 18 months or so
a drop in for another 18 months or so before I really
before I really
before I really quit so why' I drop
quit so why' I drop
quit so why' I drop out it started before I was
out it started before I was
out it started before I was born my biological mother was a young
born my biological mother was a young
born my biological mother was a young unwed graduate student and she decided
unwed graduate student and she decided
unwed graduate student and she decided to put me up for
to put me up for
to put me up for adoption she felt very strongly that I
adoption she felt very strongly that I
adoption she felt very strongly that I should be adopted by college graduates
should be adopted by college graduates
should be adopted by college graduates so everything was all set for me to be
so everything was all set for me to be
so everything was all set for me to be adopted at Birth by a lawyer and a his
adopted at Birth by a lawyer and a his
adopted at Birth by a lawyer and a his wife except that when I popped out they
wife except that when I popped out they
wife except that when I popped out they decided at the last minute that they
decided at the last minute that they
decided at the last minute that they really wanted a
really wanted a
really wanted a girl so my parents who were on a waiting
girl so my parents who were on a waiting
girl so my parents who were on a waiting list got a call in the middle of the
list got a call in the middle of the
list got a call in the middle of the night asking we've got an unexpected
night asking we've got an unexpected
night asking we've got an unexpected baby boy do you want him they said of
baby boy do you want him they said of
baby boy do you want him they said of course my biological mother found out
course my biological mother found out
course my biological mother found out later that my mother had never graduated
later that my mother had never graduated
later that my mother had never graduated from college and that my father had
from college and that my father had
from college and that my father had never graduated from high school she
never graduated from high school she
never graduated from high school she refused to signed the final adoption
refused to signed the final adoption
refused to signed the final adoption papers she only relented a few months
papers she only relented a few months
papers she only relented a few months later when my parents promised that I
later when my parents promised that I
later when my parents promised that I would go to college this was the start
would go to college this was the start
would go to college this was the start in my
in my
in my life and 17 years later I did go to
life and 17 years later I did go to
life and 17 years later I did go to college but I naively chose a college
college but I naively chose a college
college but I naively chose a college that was almost as expensive as
that was almost as expensive as
that was almost as expensive as Stanford and all of my workingclass
Stanford and all of my workingclass
Stanford and all of my workingclass parents savings were being spent on my
parents savings were being spent on my
parents savings were being spent on my college tuition after 6 months I
college tuition after 6 months I
college tuition after 6 months I couldn't see the value in it
couldn't see the value in it
couldn't see the value in it I had no idea what I wanted to do with
I had no idea what I wanted to do with
I had no idea what I wanted to do with my life and no idea how College was
my life and no idea how College was
my life and no idea how College was going to help me figure it out and here
going to help me figure it out and here
going to help me figure it out and here I was spending all the money my parents
I was spending all the money my parents
I was spending all the money my parents had saved their entire
had saved their entire
had saved their entire life so I decided to drop out and trust
life so I decided to drop out and trust
life so I decided to drop out and trust that it would all work out okay it was
that it would all work out okay it was
that it would all work out okay it was pretty scary at the time but looking
pretty scary at the time but looking
pretty scary at the time but looking back it was one of the best decisions I
back it was one of the best decisions I
back it was one of the best decisions I ever
ever
ever made the minute I dropped out I could
made the minute I dropped out I could
made the minute I dropped out I could stop taking the required classes that
stop taking the required classes that
stop taking the required classes that didn't interest me and begin dropping in
didn't interest me and begin dropping in
didn't interest me and begin dropping in on the ones that looked far more
on the ones that looked far more
on the ones that looked far more interesting it wasn't all romantic I
interesting it wasn't all romantic I
interesting it wasn't all romantic I didn't have a dorm room so I slept on
didn't have a dorm room so I slept on
didn't have a dorm room so I slept on the floor in friends rooms I returned
the floor in friends rooms I returned
the floor in friends rooms I returned Coke bottles for the 5-cent deposits to
Coke bottles for the 5-cent deposits to
Coke bottles for the 5-cent deposits to buy food with and I would walk the seven
buy food with and I would walk the seven
buy food with and I would walk the seven miles across town every Sunday night to
miles across town every Sunday night to
miles across town every Sunday night to get one good meal a week at the Hari
get one good meal a week at the Hari
get one good meal a week at the Hari Krishna Temple I loved it and much of
Krishna Temple I loved it and much of
Krishna Temple I loved it and much of what I stumbled into by following my
what I stumbled into by following my
what I stumbled into by following my curiosity and intuition turned out to be
curiosity and intuition turned out to be
curiosity and intuition turned out to be Priceless later on let me give you one
Priceless later on let me give you one
Priceless later on let me give you one example Reed College at that time
example Reed College at that time
example Reed College at that time offered perhaps the best calligraphy
offered perhaps the best calligraphy
offered perhaps the best calligraphy instruction in the country throughout
instruction in the country throughout
instruction in the country throughout the campus every poster every label on
the campus every poster every label on
the campus every poster every label on every drawer was beautifully hand
every drawer was beautifully hand
every drawer was beautifully hand cigraph because I had dropped out and
cigraph because I had dropped out and
cigraph because I had dropped out and didn't have to take the normal classes I
didn't have to take the normal classes I
didn't have to take the normal classes I decided to take a calligraphy class to
decided to take a calligraphy class to
decided to take a calligraphy class to learn how to do this I learned about
learn how to do this I learned about
learn how to do this I learned about serif and Sans serif type faces about
serif and Sans serif type faces about
serif and Sans serif type faces about varying the amount of space between
varying the amount of space between
varying the amount of space between different letter combinations about what
different letter combinations about what
different letter combinations about what makes great typography
makes great typography
makes great typography great it was beautiful historical
great it was beautiful historical
great it was beautiful historical artistically subtle in a way that
artistically subtle in a way that
artistically subtle in a way that science can't capture and I found it
science can't capture and I found it
science can't capture and I found it fascinating none of this had even a hope
fascinating none of this had even a hope
fascinating none of this had even a hope of any practical application in my
of any practical application in my
of any practical application in my life but 10 years later when we were
life but 10 years later when we were
life but 10 years later when we were designing the first Macintosh computer
designing the first Macintosh computer
designing the first Macintosh computer it all came back to me and we designed
it all came back to me and we designed
it all came back to me and we designed it all into the Mac it was the first
it all into the Mac it was the first
it all into the Mac it was the first computer with beautiful
computer with beautiful
computer with beautiful typography if I had never never dropped
typography if I had never never dropped
typography if I had never never dropped in on that single course in college the
in on that single course in college the
in on that single course in college the Mac would have never had multiple type
Mac would have never had multiple type
Mac would have never had multiple type faces or proportionately spaced fonts
faces or proportionately spaced fonts
faces or proportionately spaced fonts and since Windows just copi the Mac it's
and since Windows just copi the Mac it's
and since Windows just copi the Mac it's likely that no personal computer would
likely that no personal computer would
likely that no personal computer would have
have
them if I had never dropped out I would
them if I had never dropped out I would have never dropped in on that
have never dropped in on that
have never dropped in on that calligraphy class and personal computers
calligraphy class and personal computers
calligraphy class and personal computers might not have the wonderful typography
might not have the wonderful typography
might not have the wonderful typography that they do of course it was impossible
that they do of course it was impossible
that they do of course it was impossible to connect the dots looking forward when
to connect the dots looking forward when
to connect the dots looking forward when I was in college but it was very very
I was in college but it was very very
I was in college but it was very very clear looking backwards 10 years later
clear looking backwards 10 years later
clear looking backwards 10 years later again you can't connect the dots looking
again you can't connect the dots looking
again you can't connect the dots looking forward you can only connect them
forward you can only connect them
forward you can only connect them looking backwards so you have to trust
looking backwards so you have to trust
looking backwards so you have to trust that the dots will somehow connect in
that the dots will somehow connect in
that the dots will somehow connect in your future you have to trust in
your future you have to trust in
your future you have to trust in something your gut Destiny Life Karma
something your gut Destiny Life Karma
something your gut Destiny Life Karma whatever because believing that the dots
whatever because believing that the dots
whatever because believing that the dots will connect down the road will give you
will connect down the road will give you
will connect down the road will give you the confidence to follow your heart even
the confidence to follow your heart even
the confidence to follow your heart even when it leads you off the well-worn path
when it leads you off the well-worn path
when it leads you off the well-worn path path and that will make all the
difference my second story is about love
difference my second story is about love and
and
and loss I was lucky I found what I love to
loss I was lucky I found what I love to
loss I was lucky I found what I love to do early in life W and I started Apple
do early in life W and I started Apple
do early in life W and I started Apple in my parents garage when I was 20 we
in my parents garage when I was 20 we
in my parents garage when I was 20 we worked hard and in 10 years Apple had
worked hard and in 10 years Apple had
worked hard and in 10 years Apple had grown from Just the Two of Us in a
grown from Just the Two of Us in a
grown from Just the Two of Us in a garage into A2 billion doll company with
garage into A2 billion doll company with
garage into A2 billion doll company with over 4,000 employees we just released
over 4,000 employees we just released
over 4,000 employees we just released our finest creation the Macintosh a year
our finest creation the Macintosh a year
our finest creation the Macintosh a year earlier and I just turned
earlier and I just turned
earlier and I just turned 30 and then I got
30 and then I got
30 and then I got fired how can you get fired from a
fired how can you get fired from a
fired how can you get fired from a company you
company you
company you started well as Apple grew we hired
started well as Apple grew we hired
started well as Apple grew we hired someone who I thought was very talented
someone who I thought was very talented
someone who I thought was very talented to run the company with me and for the
to run the company with me and for the
to run the company with me and for the first year or so things went well but
first year or so things went well but
first year or so things went well but then our visions of the future began to
then our visions of the future began to
then our visions of the future began to diverge and eventually we had a falling
diverge and eventually we had a falling
diverge and eventually we had a falling out when we did our board of directors
out when we did our board of directors
out when we did our board of directors sided with him and so at 30 I was out
sided with him and so at 30 I was out
sided with him and so at 30 I was out and very publicly out what had been the
and very publicly out what had been the
and very publicly out what had been the focus of my entire adult life was gone
focus of my entire adult life was gone
focus of my entire adult life was gone and it was
and it was
and it was devastating I really didn't know what to
devastating I really didn't know what to
devastating I really didn't know what to do for a few months I felt that I had
do for a few months I felt that I had
do for a few months I felt that I had let the previous generation of
let the previous generation of
let the previous generation of entrepreneurs down that I had dropped
entrepreneurs down that I had dropped
entrepreneurs down that I had dropped the Baton as it was being passed to me I
the Baton as it was being passed to me I
the Baton as it was being passed to me I met with David Packard and Bob noise and
met with David Packard and Bob noise and
met with David Packard and Bob noise and tried to apologize for screwing up so
tried to apologize for screwing up so
tried to apologize for screwing up so badly I was a very public failure and I
badly I was a very public failure and I
badly I was a very public failure and I even thought about running away from the
even thought about running away from the
even thought about running away from the valley but something slowly began to
valley but something slowly began to
valley but something slowly began to dawn on me I still loved what I
dawn on me I still loved what I
dawn on me I still loved what I did the turn of events at Apple had not
did the turn of events at Apple had not
did the turn of events at Apple had not changed that one bit I'd been rejected
changed that one bit I'd been rejected
changed that one bit I'd been rejected but I was still in
but I was still in
but I was still in love and so I decided to start
love and so I decided to start
love and so I decided to start over I didn't see it then but it turned
over I didn't see it then but it turned
over I didn't see it then but it turned out that getting fired from Apple was
out that getting fired from Apple was
out that getting fired from Apple was the best thing that could have ever
the best thing that could have ever
the best thing that could have ever happened to me the heaviness of being
happened to me the heaviness of being
happened to me the heaviness of being successful was replaced by the lightness
successful was replaced by the lightness
successful was replaced by the lightness of being a beginner again less sure
of being a beginner again less sure
of being a beginner again less sure about everything it freed me to enter
about everything it freed me to enter
about everything it freed me to enter one of the most creative periods per of
one of the most creative periods per of
one of the most creative periods per of my life during the next 5 years I
my life during the next 5 years I
my life during the next 5 years I started a company named next another
started a company named next another
started a company named next another company named Pixar and fell in love
company named Pixar and fell in love
company named Pixar and fell in love with an amazing woman who would become
with an amazing woman who would become
with an amazing woman who would become my wife Pixar went on to create the
my wife Pixar went on to create the
my wife Pixar went on to create the world's first computer animated feature
world's first computer animated feature
world's first computer animated feature film Toy Story and is now the most
film Toy Story and is now the most
film Toy Story and is now the most successful Animation Studio in the
successful Animation Studio in the
successful Animation Studio in the world in a remarkable turn of events
world in a remarkable turn of events
world in a remarkable turn of events Apple bought next and I returned to
Apple bought next and I returned to
Apple bought next and I returned to Apple and the technology we developed it
Apple and the technology we developed it
Apple and the technology we developed it next is at the heart of Apple's current
next is at the heart of Apple's current
next is at the heart of Apple's current Renaissance and L and I have a wonderful
Renaissance and L and I have a wonderful
Renaissance and L and I have a wonderful family
family
family together I'm pretty sure none of this
together I'm pretty sure none of this
together I'm pretty sure none of this would have happened if I hadn't been
would have happened if I hadn't been
would have happened if I hadn't been fired from Apple it was awful tasting
fired from Apple it was awful tasting
fired from Apple it was awful tasting medicine but I guess the patient needed
medicine but I guess the patient needed
medicine but I guess the patient needed it sometime life sometimes life's going
it sometime life sometimes life's going
it sometime life sometimes life's going to hit you in the head with a brick
to hit you in the head with a brick
to hit you in the head with a brick don't lose faith I'm convinced that the
don't lose faith I'm convinced that the
don't lose faith I'm convinced that the only thing that kept me going was that I
only thing that kept me going was that I
only thing that kept me going was that I loved what I did you've got to find what
loved what I did you've got to find what
loved what I did you've got to find what you love and that is as true for work as
you love and that is as true for work as
you love and that is as true for work as it is for your lovers your work is going
it is for your lovers your work is going
it is for your lovers your work is going to fill a large part of your life and
to fill a large part of your life and
to fill a large part of your life and the only way to be truly satisfied is to
the only way to be truly satisfied is to
the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work and
do what you believe is great work and
do what you believe is great work and the only way to do great work is to love
the only way to do great work is to love
the only way to do great work is to love what you do if you haven't found it yet
what you do if you haven't found it yet
what you do if you haven't found it yet keep looking and don't settle as with
keep looking and don't settle as with
keep looking and don't settle as with all matters of the heart you'll know
all matters of the heart you'll know
all matters of the heart you'll know when you find it and like any great
when you find it and like any great
when you find it and like any great relationship it just gets better and
relationship it just gets better and
relationship it just gets better and better as the years roll on so keep
better as the years roll on so keep
better as the years roll on so keep looking don't settle
my third story is about
my third story is about death when I was 17 I read a quote that
death when I was 17 I read a quote that
death when I was 17 I read a quote that went something like if you live each day
went something like if you live each day
went something like if you live each day as if it was your last someday you'll
as if it was your last someday you'll
as if it was your last someday you'll most certainly be
right it made an impression on me and
right it made an impression on me and since then for the past 33 years I
since then for the past 33 years I
since then for the past 33 years I looked in the mirror every morning and
looked in the mirror every morning and
looked in the mirror every morning and asked myself if today were the last day
asked myself if today were the last day
asked myself if today were the last day of my life what I want to do what I am
of my life what I want to do what I am
of my life what I want to do what I am about to do today and whenever the
about to do today and whenever the
about to do today and whenever the answer has been no for too many days in
answer has been no for too many days in
answer has been no for too many days in a row I know I need to change
a row I know I need to change
a row I know I need to change something remembering that I'll be dead
something remembering that I'll be dead
something remembering that I'll be dead soon is the most important tool I've
soon is the most important tool I've
soon is the most important tool I've ever encountered to help me make the big
ever encountered to help me make the big
ever encountered to help me make the big choices in life because almost
choices in life because almost
choices in life because almost everything all external expectations all
everything all external expectations all
everything all external expectations all Pride all fear of embarrassment or
Pride all fear of embarrassment or
Pride all fear of embarrassment or failure these things just fall away in
failure these things just fall away in
failure these things just fall away in the face of death leaving only what is
the face of death leaving only what is
the face of death leaving only what is truly important
truly important
truly important remembering that you are going to die is
remembering that you are going to die is
remembering that you are going to die is the best way I know to avoid the Trap of
the best way I know to avoid the Trap of
the best way I know to avoid the Trap of thinking you have something to lose you
thinking you have something to lose you
thinking you have something to lose you are already naked there is no reason not
are already naked there is no reason not
are already naked there is no reason not to follow your
to follow your
to follow your heart about a year ago I was diagnosed
heart about a year ago I was diagnosed
heart about a year ago I was diagnosed with cancer I had a scan at 7:30 in the
with cancer I had a scan at 7:30 in the
with cancer I had a scan at 7:30 in the morning and it clearly showed a tumor on
morning and it clearly showed a tumor on
morning and it clearly showed a tumor on my pancreas I didn't even know what a
my pancreas I didn't even know what a
my pancreas I didn't even know what a pancreas was the doctors told me this
pancreas was the doctors told me this
pancreas was the doctors told me this was almost certainly a type of cancer
was almost certainly a type of cancer
was almost certainly a type of cancer that is incurable and that I should
that is incurable and that I should
that is incurable and that I should expect to live no longer than 3 to 6
expect to live no longer than 3 to 6
expect to live no longer than 3 to 6 months my doctor advised me to go home
months my doctor advised me to go home
months my doctor advised me to go home and get my Affairs in order which is
and get my Affairs in order which is
and get my Affairs in order which is doctor's code for prepare to die it
doctor's code for prepare to die it
doctor's code for prepare to die it means to try and tell your kids
means to try and tell your kids
means to try and tell your kids everything you thought you'd have the
everything you thought you'd have the
everything you thought you'd have the next 10 years to tell them in just a few
next 10 years to tell them in just a few
next 10 years to tell them in just a few months it means to make sure everything
months it means to make sure everything
months it means to make sure everything is buttoned up so that it will be as
is buttoned up so that it will be as
is buttoned up so that it will be as easy as possible for your family it
easy as possible for your family it
easy as possible for your family it means to say your goodbyes
means to say your goodbyes
means to say your goodbyes I live with that diagnosis all day later
I live with that diagnosis all day later
I live with that diagnosis all day later that evening I had a biopsy where they
that evening I had a biopsy where they
that evening I had a biopsy where they stuck an endoscope down my throat
stuck an endoscope down my throat
stuck an endoscope down my throat through my stomach and into my
through my stomach and into my
through my stomach and into my intestines put a needle into my pancreas
intestines put a needle into my pancreas
intestines put a needle into my pancreas and got a few cells from the tumor I was
and got a few cells from the tumor I was
and got a few cells from the tumor I was sedated but my wife who was there told
sedated but my wife who was there told
sedated but my wife who was there told me that when they viewed the cells under
me that when they viewed the cells under
me that when they viewed the cells under a microscope the doctor started crying
a microscope the doctor started crying
a microscope the doctor started crying because it turned out to be a very rare
because it turned out to be a very rare
because it turned out to be a very rare form of pancreatic cancer that is
form of pancreatic cancer that is
form of pancreatic cancer that is curable with surgery I had the surgery
curable with surgery I had the surgery
curable with surgery I had the surgery and thankfully I'm fine
now this was the closest I've been to
now this was the closest I've been to facing death and I hope it's the closest
facing death and I hope it's the closest
facing death and I hope it's the closest I get for a few more decades having
I get for a few more decades having
I get for a few more decades having lived through it I can now say this to
lived through it I can now say this to
lived through it I can now say this to you with a bit more certainty than when
you with a bit more certainty than when
you with a bit more certainty than when death was a useful but purely
death was a useful but purely
death was a useful but purely intellectual
intellectual
intellectual concept no one wants to die even people
concept no one wants to die even people
concept no one wants to die even people who want to go to heaven don't want to
who want to go to heaven don't want to
who want to go to heaven don't want to die to get there and yet death is the
die to get there and yet death is the
die to get there and yet death is the destination we all share no one has ever
destination we all share no one has ever
destination we all share no one has ever escaped it and that is as it should be
escaped it and that is as it should be
escaped it and that is as it should be because death is very likely the single
because death is very likely the single
because death is very likely the single best invention of life it's life's
best invention of life it's life's
best invention of life it's life's change agent it clears out the old to
change agent it clears out the old to
change agent it clears out the old to make way for the new right now the new
make way for the new right now the new
make way for the new right now the new is you but someday not too long from now
is you but someday not too long from now
is you but someday not too long from now you will gradually become the old and be
you will gradually become the old and be
you will gradually become the old and be cleared away sorry to be so dramatic but
cleared away sorry to be so dramatic but
cleared away sorry to be so dramatic but it's quite
it's quite
it's quite true your time is limited so don't waste
true your time is limited so don't waste
true your time is limited so don't waste it living someone else's life don't be
it living someone else's life don't be
it living someone else's life don't be trapped by Dogma which is living with
trapped by Dogma which is living with
trapped by Dogma which is living with the results of other people's thinking
the results of other people's thinking
the results of other people's thinking don't let the noise of others opinions
don't let the noise of others opinions
don't let the noise of others opinions drown out your own inner voice and most
drown out your own inner voice and most
drown out your own inner voice and most important have the courage to follow
important have the courage to follow
important have the courage to follow your heart and intuition they somehow
your heart and intuition they somehow
your heart and intuition they somehow already know what you truly want to
already know what you truly want to
already know what you truly want to become everything else is secondary
when I was young there was an amazing
when I was young there was an amazing publication called the whole earth
publication called the whole earth
publication called the whole earth catalog which was one of the Bibles of
catalog which was one of the Bibles of
catalog which was one of the Bibles of my generation it was created by a fellow
my generation it was created by a fellow
my generation it was created by a fellow named Stuart brand not far from here in
named Stuart brand not far from here in
named Stuart brand not far from here in Meno Park and he brought it to life with
Meno Park and he brought it to life with
Meno Park and he brought it to life with his poetic touch this was in the late
his poetic touch this was in the late
his poetic touch this was in the late 60s before personal computers and
60s before personal computers and
60s before personal computers and desktop publishing so it was all made
desktop publishing so it was all made
desktop publishing so it was all made with typewriters scissors and Polaroid
with typewriters scissors and Polaroid
with typewriters scissors and Polaroid cameras it was sort of like Google in
cameras it was sort of like Google in
cameras it was sort of like Google in paperback form 35 years before Google
paperback form 35 years before Google
paperback form 35 years before Google came along it was idealistic overflowing
came along it was idealistic overflowing
came along it was idealistic overflowing with neat tools and great
with neat tools and great
with neat tools and great Notions Stewart and his team put out
Notions Stewart and his team put out
Notions Stewart and his team put out several issues of the whole earth
several issues of the whole earth
several issues of the whole earth catalog and then when it had run its
catalog and then when it had run its
catalog and then when it had run its course they put out a final issue it was
course they put out a final issue it was
course they put out a final issue it was the mid 1970s and I was your
the mid 1970s and I was your
the mid 1970s and I was your age on the back cover of their final
age on the back cover of their final
age on the back cover of their final issue was a photograph of an early
issue was a photograph of an early
issue was a photograph of an early morning Country Road the kind you might
morning Country Road the kind you might
morning Country Road the kind you might find yourself hitchhiking on if you were
find yourself hitchhiking on if you were
find yourself hitchhiking on if you were so
so
so adventurous beneath it were the words
adventurous beneath it were the words
adventurous beneath it were the words stay hungry stay foolish it was their
stay hungry stay foolish it was their
stay hungry stay foolish it was their farewell message as they signed off stay
farewell message as they signed off stay
farewell message as they signed off stay hungry stay foolish and I have always
hungry stay foolish and I have always
hungry stay foolish and I have always wished that for
wished that for
wished that for myself and now as you graduate to begin
myself and now as you graduate to begin
myself and now as you graduate to begin a new I wish that for you stay hungry
a new I wish that for you stay hungry
a new I wish that for you stay hungry stay foolish thank you all very
stay foolish thank you all very
much the preceding program is
much the preceding program is copyrighted by Stanford University
copyrighted by Stanford University
copyrighted by Stanford University please visit us at stanford.edu